father = [{"question":"與","Answer":"yǔ"},
{"question":"父親","Answer":"fǔqīn"},
{"question":"已有","Answer":"yǐyǒu"},
{"question":"兩年","Answer":"liǎngnián"},
{"question":"多","Answer":"duō"},
{"question":"沒","Answer":"méi"},
{"question":"見面","Answer":"jiànmiàn"},
{"question":"了","Answer":"le"},
{"question":"我","Answer":"wǒ"},
{"question":"最","Answer":"zuì"},
{"question":"不能","Answer":"bùnéng"},
{"question":"忘記","Answer":"wàngjì"},
{"question":"的","Answer":"de"},
{"question":"是","Answer":"shì"},
{"question":"他","Answer":"tā"},
{"question":"的","Answer":"de"},
{"question":"背影","Answer":"bèiyǐng"},
{"question":"那年","Answer":"nànián"},
{"question":"冬天","Answer":"dōngtiān"},
{"question":"祖母","Answer":"zǔmǔ"},
{"question":"死","Answer":"sǐ"},
{"question":"了","Answer":"le"},
{"question":"我","Answer":"wǒ"},
{"question":"從","Answer":"cóng"},
{"question":"北京","Answer":"běijīng"},
{"question":"回家","Answer":"huíjiā"},
{"question":"奔喪","Answer":"bēnsāng"},
{"question":"喪事","Answer":"sāngshì"},
{"question":"完畢","Answer":"wánbì"},
{"question":"父親","Answer":"fùqīn"},
{"question":"要到","Answer":"yàodào"},
{"question":"南京","Answer":"nánjīng"},
{"question":"工作","Answer":"gōngzuò"},
{"question":"我","Answer":"wǒ"},
{"question":"也要","Answer":"yěyào"},
{"question":"回到","Answer":"huídào"},
{"question":"北京","Answer":"běijīng"},
{"question":"唸書","Answer":"niànshū"},
{"question":"我們","Answer":"wǒmen"},
{"question":"便","Answer":"biàn"},
{"question":"同行","Answer":"tóngxíng"},
{"question":"到","Answer":"dào"},
{"question":"南京","Answer":"nánjīng"},
{"question":"時","Answer":"shí"},
{"question":"父親","Answer":"fùqīn"},
{"question":"因為","Answer":"yīnwèi"},
{"question":"事","Answer":"shì"},
{"question":"忙","Answer":"máng"},
{"question":"本","Answer":"běn"},
{"question":"已","Answer":"yǐ"},
{"question":"說定","Answer":"shuōdìng"},
{"question":"不送","Answer":"búsòng"},
{"question":"我","Answer":"wǒ"},
{"question":"但","Answer":"dàn"},
{"question":"他","Answer":"tā"},
{"question":"終於","Answer":"zhōngyú"},
{"question":"不放","Answer":"búfàng"},
{"question":"心","Answer":"xīn"},
{"question":"決定","Answer":"juédìng"},
{"question":"還是","Answer":"háishì"},
{"question":"送","Answer":"sòng"},
{"question":"我","Answer":"wǒ"},
{"question":"上火","Answer":"shànghuǒ"},
{"question":"車","Answer":"chē"},
{"question":"上","Answer":"shàng"},
{"question":"了","Answer":"le"},
{"question":"火車","Answer":"huǒchē"},
{"question":"他","Answer":"tā"},
{"question":"給","Answer":"gěi"},
{"question":"我","Answer":"wǒ"},
{"question":"揀","Answer":"jiǎn"},
{"question":"了","Answer":"le"},
{"question":"靠","Answer":"kào"},
{"question":"車門","Answer":"chēmén"},
{"question":"的","Answer":"de"},
{"question":"一張","Answer":"yìzhāng"},
{"question":"椅子","Answer":"yǐzi"},
{"question":"他","Answer":"tā"},
{"question":"囑","Answer":"zhǔ"},
{"question":"我","Answer":"wǒ"},
{"question":"路上","Answer":"lùshàng"},
{"question":"小心","Answer":"xiǎoxīn"},
{"question":"夜","Answer":"yè"},
{"question":"裏","Answer":"lǐ"},
{"question":"要","Answer":"yào"},
{"question":"警醒","Answer":"jǐngxǐng"},
{"question":"些","Answer":"xiē"},
{"question":"不要","Answer":"búyào"},
{"question":"受涼","Answer":"shòuliáng"},
{"question":"我","Answer":"wǒ"},
{"question":"說道","Answer":"shuōdào"},
{"question":"爸爸","Answer":"bàba"},
{"question":"你","Answer":"nǐ"},
{"question":"走","Answer":"zǒu"},
{"question":"吧","Answer":"ba"},
{"question":"他","Answer":"tā"},
{"question":"往","Answer":"wǎng"},
{"question":"車外","Answer":"chēwài"},
{"question":"看","Answer":"kàn"},
{"question":"了","Answer":"le"},
{"question":"看","Answer":"kàn"},
{"question":"說","Answer":"shuō"},
{"question":"我","Answer":"wǒ"},
{"question":"買","Answer":"mǎi"},
{"question":"幾個","Answer":"jǐge"},
{"question":"橘子","Answer":"júzi"},
{"question":"去","Answer":"qù"},
{"question":"你","Answer":"nǐ"},
{"question":"就","Answer":"jiù"},
{"question":"在此","Answer":"zàicǐ"},
{"question":"地","Answer":"dì"},
{"question":"不要","Answer":"búyào"},
{"question":"走動","Answer":"zǒudòng"},
{"question":"我","Answer":"wǒ"},
{"question":"望","Answer":"wàng"},
{"question":"向","Answer":"xiàng"},
{"question":"那邊","Answer":"nàbiān"},
{"question":"月台","Answer":"yuètái"},
{"question":"柵欄","Answer":"zhàlán"},
{"question":"外","Answer":"wài"},
{"question":"有","Answer":"yǒu"},
{"question":"幾個","Answer":"jǐge"},
{"question":"賣東西","Answer":"màidōngxī"},
{"question":"的","Answer":"de"},
{"question":"在","Answer":"zài"},
{"question":"等","Answer":"děng"},
{"question":"着","Answer":"zhe"},
{"question":"顧客","Answer":"gùkè"},
{"question":"走到","Answer":"zǒudào"},
{"question":"那邊","Answer":"nàbiān"},
{"question":"月台","Answer":"yuètái"},
{"question":"須","Answer":"xū"},
{"question":"穿過","Answer":"chuānguò"},
{"question":"鐵道","Answer":"tiědào"},
{"question":"須","Answer":"xū"},
{"question":"跳下去","Answer":"tiàoxiàqù"},
{"question":"又","Answer":"yòu"},
{"question":"爬上去","Answer":"páshàngqù"},
{"question":"父親","Answer":"fùqīn"},
{"question":"是","Answer":"shì"},
{"question":"一個","Answer":"yígè"},
{"question":"胖子","Answer":"pàngzi"},
{"question":"走過","Answer":"zǒuguò"},
{"question":"去","Answer":"qù"},
{"question":"自然","Answer":"zìrán"},
{"question":"要","Answer":"yào"},
{"question":"費事","Answer":"fèishì"},
{"question":"些","Answer":"xiē"},
{"question":"我","Answer":"wǒ"},
{"question":"本來","Answer":"běnlái"},
{"question":"要","Answer":"yào"},
{"question":"去","Answer":"qù"},
{"question":"的","Answer":"de"},
{"question":"他","Answer":"tā"},
{"question":"不肯","Answer":"bùkěn"},
{"question":"只好","Answer":"zhǐhǎo"},
{"question":"讓","Answer":"ràng"},
{"question":"他","Answer":"tā"},
{"question":"去","Answer":"qù"},
{"question":"我","Answer":"wǒ"},
{"question":"看見","Answer":"kànjiàn"},
{"question":"他","Answer":"tā"},
{"question":"戴","Answer":"dài"},
{"question":"着","Answer":"zhe"},
{"question":"黑布","Answer":"hēibù"},
{"question":"小帽","Answer":"xiǎomào"},
{"question":"穿著","Answer":"chuānzhuó"},
{"question":"黑布","Answer":"hēibù"},
{"question":"大馬","Answer":"dàmǎ"},
{"question":"褂","Answer":"guà"},
{"question":"深","Answer":"shēn"},
{"question":"青","Answer":"qīng"},
{"question":"布","Answer":"bù"},
{"question":"棉袍","Answer":"miánpáo"},
{"question":"蹣跚","Answer":"mánshān"},
{"question":"地","Answer":"dì"},
{"question":"走到","Answer":"zǒudào"},
{"question":"鐡","Answer":"tiě"},
{"question":"道","Answer":"dào"},
{"question":"邊","Answer":"biān"},
{"question":"慢慢","Answer":"mànmàn"},
{"question":"探身","Answer":"tànshēn"},
{"question":"下去","Answer":"xiàqù"},
{"question":"尚","Answer":"shàng"},
{"question":"不大","Answer":"búdà"},
{"question":"難","Answer":"nán"},
{"question":"可是","Answer":"kěshì"},
{"question":"他","Answer":"tā"},
{"question":"穿過","Answer":"chuānguò"},
{"question":"鐵道","Answer":"tiědào"},
{"question":"要","Answer":"yào"},
{"question":"爬上","Answer":"páshàng"},
{"question":"那邊","Answer":"nàbiān"},
{"question":"月台","Answer":"yuètái"},
{"question":"就","Answer":"jiù"},
{"question":"不容易","Answer":"bùróngyì"},
{"question":"了","Answer":"le"},
{"question":"他用","Answer":"tāyòng"},
{"question":"兩手","Answer":"liǎngshǒu"},
{"question":"攀","Answer":"pān"},
{"question":"着","Answer":"zhe"},
{"question":"上面","Answer":"shàngmiàn"},
{"question":"兩","Answer":"liǎng"},
{"question":"腳","Answer":"jiǎo"},
{"question":"再","Answer":"zài"},
{"question":"向上","Answer":"xiàngshàng"},
{"question":"縮","Answer":"suō"},
{"question":"他","Answer":"tā"},
{"question":"肥胖","Answer":"féipàng"},
{"question":"的","Answer":"de"},
{"question":"身子","Answer":"shēnzi"},
{"question":"向","Answer":"xiàng"},
{"question":"左","Answer":"zuǒ"},
{"question":"微","Answer":"wéi"},
{"question":"傾","Answer":"qīng"},
{"question":"顯出","Answer":"xiǎnchū"},
{"question":"努力","Answer":"nǔlì"},
{"question":"的","Answer":"de"},
{"question":"樣子","Answer":"yàngzi"},
{"question":"我","Answer":"wǒ"},
{"question":"看","Answer":"kàn"},
{"question":"着","Answer":"zhe"},
{"question":"他","Answer":"tā"},
{"question":"的","Answer":"de"},
{"question":"背影","Answer":"bèiyǐng"},
{"question":"眼淚","Answer":"yǎnlèi"},
{"question":"很快","Answer":"hěnkuài"},
{"question":"地","Answer":"de"},
{"question":"流下來","Answer":"liúxiàlai"},
{"question":"了","Answer":"le"},
{"question":"我","Answer":"wǒ"},
{"question":"趕緊","Answer":"gǎnjǐn"},
{"question":"拭乾","Answer":"shìgān"},
{"question":"了","Answer":"le"},
{"question":"淚","Answer":"lèi"},
{"question":"怕","Answer":"pà"},
{"question":"他","Answer":"tā"},
{"question":"看見","Answer":"kànjiàn"},
{"question":"也","Answer":"yě"},
{"question":"怕","Answer":"pà"},
{"question":"別人","Answer":"biérén"},
{"question":"看見","Answer":"kànjiàn"},
{"question":"當","Answer":"dāng"},
{"question":"我","Answer":"wǒ"},
{"question":"再","Answer":"zài"},
{"question":"向外看","Answer":"xiàngwàikàn"},
{"question":"時","Answer":"shí"},
{"question":"他","Answer":"tā"},
{"question":"已","Answer":"yǐ"},
{"question":"抱","Answer":"bào"},
{"question":"了","Answer":"le"},
{"question":"朱紅","Answer":"zhūhóng"},
{"question":"的","Answer":"de"},
{"question":"橘子","Answer":"júzi"},
{"question":"往","Answer":"wǎng"},
{"question":"回","Answer":"huí"},
{"question":"走","Answer":"zǒu"},
{"question":"了","Answer":"le"},
{"question":"過","Answer":"guò"},
{"question":"鐵道","Answer":"tiědào"},
{"question":"時","Answer":"shí"},
{"question":"他","Answer":"tā"},
{"question":"先","Answer":"xiān"},
{"question":"將","Answer":"jiāng"},
{"question":"橘子","Answer":"júzi"},
{"question":"散","Answer":"sàn"},
{"question":"放在","Answer":"fàngzài"},
{"question":"地上","Answer":"dìshàng"},
{"question":"自己","Answer":"zìjǐ"},
{"question":"慢慢","Answer":"mànmàn"},
{"question":"爬下","Answer":"páxia"},
{"question":"再","Answer":"zài"},
{"question":"抱起","Answer":"bàoqǐ"},
{"question":"橘子","Answer":"júzi"},
{"question":"走","Answer":"zǒu"},
{"question":"到","Answer":"dào"},
{"question":"這邊","Answer":"zhèbiān"},
{"question":"時","Answer":"shí"},
{"question":"我","Answer":"wǒ"},
{"question":"趕緊","Answer":"gǎnjǐn"},
{"question":"去","Answer":"qù"},
{"question":"攙扶","Answer":"chānfú"},
{"question":"他","Answer":"tā"},
{"question":"他","Answer":"tā"},
{"question":"和","Answer":"hè"},
{"question":"我","Answer":"wǒ"},
{"question":"走到","Answer":"zǒudào"},
{"question":"車上","Answer":"chēshàng"},
{"question":"將","Answer":"jiāng"},
{"question":"橘子","Answer":"júzi"},
{"question":"放在","Answer":"fàngzài"},
{"question":"我","Answer":"wǒ"},
{"question":"的","Answer":"de"},
{"question":"皮大衣","Answer":"pídàyī"},
{"question":"上","Answer":"shàng"},
{"question":"然後","Answer":"ránhòu"},
{"question":"撲","Answer":"pū"},
{"question":"撲","Answer":"pū"},
{"question":"衣服","Answer":"yīfú"},
{"question":"上","Answer":"shàng"},
{"question":"的","Answer":"de"},
{"question":"泥土","Answer":"nítǔ"},
{"question":"心","Answer":"xīn"},
{"question":"裏","Answer":"lǐ"},
{"question":"很","Answer":"hěn"},
{"question":"輕鬆","Answer":"qīngsōng"},
{"question":"似的","Answer":"sìde"},
{"question":"過","Answer":"guò"},
{"question":"一會","Answer":"yìhuǐ"},
{"question":"說","Answer":"shuō"},
{"question":"我","Answer":"wǒ"},
{"question":"走","Answer":"zǒu"},
{"question":"了","Answer":"le"},
{"question":"到了","Answer":"dàole"},
{"question":"那邊","Answer":"nàbiān"},
{"question":"記得","Answer":"jìde"},
{"question":"給","Answer":"gěi"},
{"question":"我","Answer":"wǒ"},
{"question":"來信","Answer":"láixìn"},
{"question":"我","Answer":"wǒ"},
{"question":"看","Answer":"kàn"},
{"question":"着","Answer":"zhe"},
{"question":"他","Answer":"tā"},
{"question":"走出","Answer":"zǒuchū"},
{"question":"去","Answer":"qù"},
{"question":"他","Answer":"tā"},
{"question":"走","Answer":"zǒu"},
{"question":"了","Answer":"le"},
{"question":"幾步","Answer":"jǐbù"},
{"question":"回過","Answer":"huíguò"},
{"question":"頭","Answer":"tóu"},
{"question":"看見","Answer":"kànjiàn"},
{"question":"我","Answer":"wǒ"},
{"question":"說","Answer":"shuō"},
{"question":"進去","Answer":"jìnqù"},
{"question":"吧","Answer":"ba"},
{"question":"等","Answer":"děng"},
{"question":"他","Answer":"tā"},
{"question":"的","Answer":"de"},
{"question":"背影","Answer":"bèiyǐng"},
{"question":"混入","Answer":"hùnrù"},
{"question":"來來往往","Answer":"láiláiwǎngwǎng"},
{"question":"的","Answer":"de"},
{"question":"人","Answer":"rén"},
{"question":"羣","Answer":"qún"},
{"question":"裹","Answer":"guǒ"},
{"question":"再","Answer":"zài"},
{"question":"找不著","Answer":"zhǎobùzháo"},
{"question":"了","Answer":"le"},
{"question":"我","Answer":"wǒ"},
{"question":"才","Answer":"cái"},
{"question":"進","Answer":"jìn"},
{"question":"車廂","Answer":"chēxiāng"},
{"question":"內","Answer":"nèi"},
{"question":"坐下","Answer":"zuòxià"},
{"question":"我","Answer":"wǒ"},
{"question":"的","Answer":"de"},
{"question":"眼淚","Answer":"yǎnlèi"},
{"question":"又來了","Answer":"yòuláile"},
{"question":"我","Answer":"wǒ"},
{"question":"回","Answer":"huí"},
{"question":"北京","Answer":"běijīng"},
{"question":"後","Answer":"hòu"},
{"question":"收到","Answer":"shōudào"},
{"question":"了","Answer":"le"},
{"question":"父親","Answer":"fùqīn"},
{"question":"寫","Answer":"xiě"},
{"question":"的","Answer":"de"},
{"question":"一封信","Answer":"yìfēngxìn"},
{"question":"信","Answer":"xìn"},
{"question":"中","Answer":"zhōng"},
{"question":"說道","Answer":"shuōdào"},
{"question":"我","Answer":"wǒ"},
{"question":"身體","Answer":"shēntǐ"},
{"question":"不安","Answer":"bù'ān"},
{"question":"只是","Answer":"zhǐshì"},
{"question":"膀子","Answer":"bǎngzi"},
{"question":"疼痛","Answer":"téngtòng"},
{"question":"厲害","Answer":"lìhài"},
{"question":"拿","Answer":"ná"},
{"question":"筷子","Answer":"kuàizi"},
{"question":"提筆","Answer":"tíbǐ"},
{"question":"諸多","Answer":"zhūduō"},
{"question":"不便","Answer":"búbiàn"},
{"question":"大約","Answer":"dàyuē"},
{"question":"大","Answer":"dà"},
{"question":"去","Answer":"qù"},
{"question":"之","Answer":"zhī"},
{"question":"期","Answer":"qí"},
{"question":"不","Answer":"bù"},
{"question":"遠","Answer":"yuǎn"},
{"question":"矣","Answer":"yǐ"},
{"question":"我","Answer":"wǒ"},
{"question":"讀到","Answer":"dúdào"},
{"question":"此處","Answer":"cǐchù"},
{"question":"在","Answer":"zài"},
{"question":"晶瑩","Answer":"jīngyíng"},
{"question":"的","Answer":"de"},
{"question":"淚光","Answer":"lèiguāng"},
{"question":"中","Answer":"zhōng"},
{"question":"又","Answer":"yòu"},
{"question":"看見","Answer":"kànjiàn"},
{"question":"那","Answer":"nà"},
{"question":"肥胖","Answer":"féipàng"},
{"question":"的","Answer":"de"},
{"question":"身穿","Answer":"shēnchuān"},
{"question":"青","Answer":"qīng"},
{"question":"布","Answer":"bù"},
{"question":"棉袍","Answer":"miánpáo"},
{"question":"黑布","Answer":"hēibù"},
{"question":"馬褂","Answer":"mǎguà"},
{"question":"的","Answer":"de"},
{"question":"背影","Answer":"bèiyǐng"},
{"question":"唉","Answer":"āi"},
{"question":"我","Answer":"wǒ"},
{"question":"不知","Answer":"bùzhī"},
{"question":"何時","Answer":"héshí"},
{"question":"再","Answer":"zài"},
{"question":"能","Answer":"néng"},
{"question":"與","Answer":"yǔ"},
{"question":"他","Answer":"tā"},
{"question":"相見","Answer":"xiāngjiàn"}]